// questions for the quiz

const quizQuestions = [{
    question: "In the Disney story, 'The Little Mermaid' which of the following is not Trition's daughter?",
    answers: [
        {option: 'Andrina'},
        {option: 'Attina'},
        {option: 'Adora'},
        {option: 'Allana'}
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Adora'
},
{
    question: "What does the enchanted cake in 'Brave' turn Merida's mother into?",
    answers: [
        {option: "A Cat"},
        {option: "A Bear"},
        {option: "A Lion"},
        {option: "A Snake"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A Bear"
},
{
    question: "What had Cinderella left behind at the ball?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Ring"},
        {option: "Glass Shoe"},
        {option: "Scarf"},
        {option: "Tiara"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Glass Shoe"
},
{
    question: "How many brothers did the character Hans have in Frozen?",
    answers: [
        {option: "5"},
        {option: "10"},
        {option: "12"},
        {option: "6"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "12"
},
{
    question: "For how many years did the Genie in Aladdin say, he got trapped in the lamp?",
    answers: [
        {option: "100 years"},
        {option: "10,000 years"},
        {option: "1000 years"},
        {option: "500 years"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "10,000 years"
},
{
    question: "What name did Ursula use when she became a human in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Vanessa"},
        {option: "Alexis"},
        {option: "Cathy"},
        {option: "Bella"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Vanessa"
},
{
    question: "How many dwarfs are there in Snow White?",
    answers: [
        {option: "4"},
        {option: "8"},
        {option: "7"},
        {option: "10"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "7"
},
{
    question: "What is the name of the princess in Aladdin?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Feline"},
        {option: "Tink"},
        {option: "Ella"},
        {option: "Jasmine"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Jasmine"
},
{
    question: "Who put Buzz's arm back together?",
    answers: [
        {option: "The Mutant Toys"},
        {option: "Woody"},
        {option: "Sid"},
        {option: "Molly"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Mutant Toys"
},
{
    question: "What is Peter Pan's sidekick's name",
    answers: [
        {option: "Wendy"},
        {option: "Dinah"},
        {option: "Alice"},
        {option: "Tinker Bell"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Tinker Bell"
}];